https://www.phillips-safety.com/privacy-policy/

×
0
Call Us 1-866-575-1307
My Account
MenuOpen SearchCall UsService EmailMy AccountGo To Cart   HomeLaser
Laser Safety Glasses
Glass Filter Lenses For Safety GlassesPolycarbonate Filter LensesAlignment Filters For Safety GlassesSpecialty Laser GogglesLaser Safety Face ShieldsIPL Safety Glasses & Patient ProtectionPrescription Laser Safety Glasses
Laser Strike Eyewear
Green BeamBlue Green BeamBlue Green Red Beam
Specialty Safety Glasses
Forensic GlassesHydrospecs Growers Glasses
Popular Laser Quick Links
Co2 LaserYag laserHolmiumAlexandrite/DiodeGreen Beam AKP/ArgonExcimer Laser
Laser Windows and Sheeting
Polymer Laser Window SheetingLaser Filter GlassLaser Window Film
Laser Warning SignsLaser BarriersRadiation/Laser Combination Glasses
Radiation
Radiation Glasses
Wrap Around Radiation GlassesEconomy Radiation GlassesFitover Radiation GlassesPlastic Radiation GlassesMetal Radiation GlassesRadiation GogglesRadiation Face Masks
Nike Radiation GlassesWiley X Radiation Glasses
Barriers and Shields
Mobile Radiation BarriersRadiation Hanging BarrierPorta ShieldsDrapes
Leaded Apron RacksLead Markers
Nuclear Medicine Shielding and StorageLead SheetingShielding GlassRadiation Warning Signs
Welding
Welding Lenses
Athermal Green LensesGold Welding LensesAlloweld LensesSuper Blue Drop In LensesSuper Magenta Drop In LensesCobalt Blue LensesClear Cover PlateWelding Magnifier
Clip-On Flip-Up Welding Safety Eyewear
Torching and Brazing Eyewear
Window Sheeting
Glass Blowing
Glass Working Safety Eyewear
Phillips202 GlassesSodium Flare PolycarbonateBoroTruView GlassesBoroView GlassesLampworking Split LensesQuartz Working GlassesShields, Visors, & WindowsPrescription Glass Working Glasses
Mashers
Multi-Stoppers
Medical
Dental LoupesPatient Transfer BoardsToboggan Arm BoardsSplash ShieldFace Masks
Optical Filters
Optical Filter GlassPolymer Filters
Industrial Glass
Laminated Safety GlassFused QuartzBorosilicate GlassFabricated Glass
Safety Glasses
General Safety GlassesPhotochromic Safety GlassesPhotochromic Bifocal Safety GlassesForensic GlassesHydrospecs Growers GlassesGlass Safety GlassesSolar Eclipse GlassesSafety Reading GlassesBifocal Safety GlassesUVC Cleaning Light Glasses
Accessories
CasesRetainer CordsAnti-Fog ProductsCleaning ProductsEyeglass RepairFrame Parts
Information
About UsBlogContact UsShipping InformationFAQShopping Q & AReturn PolicyOrders and ReturnsTerms and ConditionsTerms of UseBecome a DistributorAffiliate ProgramResource Center
Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.phillips-safety.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
© RX Safety - Developed by ISEA Media & Cosmick Technologies
